{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_Dell",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Texas_at_Austin",
    "human_readable": "Michael Dell's alma mater is University of Texas at Austin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8248274326324463,
            "question": "Name the university that Michael Dell attended."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7213398218154907,
            "question": "What is the name of Michael Dell's alma mater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6892484426498413,
            "question": "What university is Michael Dell associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6531409025192261,
            "question": "Where did Michael Dell go to university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6153978109359741,
            "question": "What is the full name of the university Michael Dell attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5632323622703552,
            "question": "Which university awarded Michael Dell his degree?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5364176630973816,
            "question": "Which educational institution is significant to Michael Dell's background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5352820158004761,
            "question": "What institution did Michael Dell graduate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4044804871082306,
            "question": "Where did Michael Dell receive his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3598606586456299,
            "question": "To what institution did Michael Dell attend for higher education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Dell's alma mater is University of Texas at Austin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3924_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Michael Dell receive his education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3924_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What institution did Michael Dell graduate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3924_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which educational institution is significant to Michael Dell's background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3924_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3924_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3924_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3924_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3924_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3924_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3924_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3924_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3924_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3924_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3924_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nReasoning:\n\n* The first document mentions that \"Dell, who attended The University of Texas at Austin during the 1980s...\"\n* The second document also mentions that \"The University of Texas at Austin... is proud of its history and strong relationship with Michael Dell...\" and later says \"Dell, who attended The University of Texas at Austin during the 1980s...\"\n* There are no documents that contradict this information.\n\nTherefore, the triple \"Michael Dell's alma mater is University of Texas at Austin\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Michael Dell's alma mater is University of Texas at Austin.\" This can be seen from multiple references in the provided text, such as:\n\n- Directly stating: \"Dell, who attended The University of Texas at Austin during the 1980s\"\n- Mentioning his involvement with the university: \"The University of Texas at Austin is proud of its history and strong relationship with Michael Dell and we\u2019re very pleased that he has agreed to be our commencement speaker this year,\" said Dr. Larry R. Faulkner, president of The University of Texas at Austin.\n- Referencing his successful career post-university, showing a direct link to his time there: \"In 18 years, the company's sales have grown to $35.4 billion. Today, Dell has more than 39,000 employees in offices and manufacturing facilities worldwide to serve its customers around the globe.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}